<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ryuuganime id="000002" version="1.2-r">
    <title>
        <native>ソードアート・オンライン アリシゼーション</native>
        <en_Latn>Sword Art Online: Alicization</en_Latn>
        <ar_001>سوارد ارت اونلاين اليزيشن</ar_001>
        <id_ID>Sword Art Online: Alisizasi</id_ID>
        <en_US>Sword Art Online: Alicization</en_US>
        <ja_JP>ソードアート・オンライン アリシゼーション</ja_JP>
        <de_DE>Sword Art Online: Alicization</de_DE>
        <ko_KR>소드 아트 온라인 앨리시제이션</ko_KR>
        <fr_FR>Sword Art Online: Alicization</fr_FR>
        <pt_PT>Sword Art Online: Alicization</pt_PT>
        <ru_RU>Мастера Меча Онлайн: Алисизация</ru_RU>
        <es_ES>Sword Art Online: Alicization</es_ES>
        <zh_Hans>刀剑神域 爱丽丝篇</zh_Hans>
        <zh_Hant>刀劍神域 愛麗絲篇</zh_Hant>
        <vi_VN>Sword Art Online: Alicization</vi_VN>
    </title>
    <backdrop>https://www.anime-planet.com/images/anime/screenshots/sword-art-online-alicization-9199-1.jpg?t=1544545041</backdrop>
    <visualKey>https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/posters/259640-19.jpg</visualKey>
    <synopsis>
        <ar_001>قصة أنمي Sword Art Online: Alicization تبدأ عندما يستيقظ كيريتو في غابة واسعة خيالية مليئة بالأشجار الشاهقة، خلال بحثه عن أدلة على حقيقة محيطه يصادف صبيًّا صغيرًا يبدو أنه يعرفه، وهم في خضم بحثهم عن والدي الصبيّ، يجد كيريتو ذكريات غريبة تعود إليه كذكرى من طفولته، وفي هذه الذكرى، يرى شخصًا آخر غير الصبيّ، وهي فتاة شابة صغيرة، اسمها أليس، وهو اسم يجب ألا يُنسى أبدًا</ar_001>
        <id_ID>Ketika Kirito terbangun, dia berada di kedalaman hutan yang sangat luas dan penuh dengan pepohonan yang menjulang tinggi. Dalam pencariannya untuk menemukan petunjuk di sekitarnya, Kirito bertemu dengan seorang anak laki-laki yang sepertinya mengenal dirinya. Anak itu seharusnya NPC biasa, namun ternyata dia memiliki perasaan layaknya manusia. Saat mereka mencari orang tua dari anak itu, Kirito mulai mengingat kenangan-kenangan yang aneh. Kenangan masa kecilnya, tentang anak laki-laki, anak perempuan berambut emas, dan nama yang seharusnya tidak pernah dia lupakan, Alice.</id_ID>
        <en_US>Kirito awakens in a vast, fantastical forest filled with towering trees. In his search for clues to the truth of his surroundings, he encounters a young boy who seems to know him. He ought to be a simple NPC, but the depth of his emotions seem no different than a human. As they search for the boy's parents, Kirito finds a peculiar memory returning to him. A memory from his own childhood, of this boy and a girl, too, with golden hair, and a name he should have never forgotten... Alice.</en_US>
        <ja_JP>「ここは……どこだ……？」 気づけばキリトは、なぜか壮大なファンタジーテイストの仮想世界にフルダイブしていた。ログイン直後の記憶があやふやなまま、手がかりを求めて辺りを彷徨う。 そして、漆黒の巨木《ギガスシダー》のもとにたどり着いた彼は、一人の少年と出会う。 「僕の名前はユージオ。よろしくキリト君」 少年は仮想世界の住人――《NPC》にもかかわらず、人間と同じ《感情の豊かさ》を持ち合わせていた。 ユージオと親交を深めながら、この世界からのログアウトを模索するキリト。 そんな彼の脳裏に、ある記憶がよみがえる。 それは、幼少期のキリトとユージオが野山を駆け回る想い出――本来、あるはずのない記憶。更にその想い出には、ユージオともう一人、金髪の髪を持つ少女の姿があった。 名前は、アリス。 絶対に忘れてはいけないはずの、大切な名前――。</ja_JP>
        <de_DE>Als Kirito in einem riesigen Wald erwacht, umgeben von einer atemberaubenden Kulisse aus gewaltigen Bäumen, bemerkt er, dass er nur noch eine verschwommene Erinnerung daran hat, was vor seinem Einloggen in die virtuelle Welt geschehen ist. Auf der Suche nach Hinweisen beginnt er den Wald zu erkunden und trifft vor der großen Zeder auf einen Jungen namens Eugeo, der Kirito bereits zu kennen scheint. Obwohl es sich bei dem Jungen um einen Non Player Character handeln muss, besitzt er dieselbe Tiefe und Komplexität an Emotionen wie ein menschliches Wesen. Die beiden machen sich auf die Suche nach seinen Eltern, bis Kirito plötzlich eine Erinnerung, die tief in ihm verborgen lag, wiedererlangt – eine Erinnerung aus seiner eigenen Kindheit! Darin läuft er gemeinsam mit Eugeo durch den Wald und an seiner Seite ist ein Mädchen mit goldenen Haaren, das den Namen Alice trägt. Doch wer ist diese mysteriöse Alice, deren Name nie hätte vergessen werden sollen?</de_DE>
        <ko_KR>키리토는 의문의 가상세계에 로그인 된 뒤 잃어버린 기억의 실마리를 찾기 위해 떠돌기 시작한다. 그곳에서 가상세계의 주민이지만 인간처럼 풍부한 감정을 지닌 유지오를 만나게 된다.</ko_KR>
        <fr_FR>A la demande de Seijirô Kikuoka, Kazuto est choisi pour tester un tout nouveau projet de Rath inspiré en parti du projet Medicuboid. Ce dernier, baptisé Soul Translator, lui permet d'accéder à un tout nouveau monde virtuel : l'Underworld.
Lors de sa toute première immersion, Kirito prend une apparence enfantine et fait la connaissance d'Alice et Eugeo, qui semblent avoir le même "âge" que lui. Les trois enfants sympathisent mais les choses se gâtent quand Alice est enlevée pour avoir violé l'une des règles de ce monde tandis que Kirito doit se déconnecter.

Plus tard, alors qu'il raccompagne Asuna chez elle, Kazuto est attaqué par un ancien membre des Laughing Coffin, qui parvient à lui injecter une dose de succinylcholine. Entre la vie et la mort, il n'a plus qu'une seule chance de survie : le Soul Translator ! Mais lors de sa nouvelle immersion, les choses ont bien changé dans le monde d'Alice.</fr_FR>
        <pt_PT />
        <ru_RU>Кирито просыпается в гуще огромного, фантастического леса. В попытках разузнать, как он там очутился, он встречает мальчика, который, кажется, знает его. Он должен быть обычным NPC, но его эмоции ничуть не отличаются от человеческих. Со временем к Кирито возвращаются некие воспоминания. Воспоминания из его детства, об этом мальчике и девочке с золотыми, как солнце, волосами, и именем, которое он никогда не должен забыть, — Алиса.</ru_RU>
        <es_ES>El Soul Translator es una interfaz que interactúa directamente con el fluctlight del usuario, algo así como el alma humana, y difiere fundamentalmente del método anterior de envío de señales al cerebro. El instituto RATH apunta a perfeccionarlo con la ayuda de Kazuto Kirigaya, que trabaja allí como empleado a tiempo parcial para probar las capacidades del sistema. Según el contrato de confidencialidad, cualquier recuerdo creado por la máquina en el mundo virtual se borra al regresar al mundo real y Kazuto sólo puede recordar vagamente un solo nombre, Alice, que le produce inquietud. Cuando Kazuto acompaña a Asuna Yuuki a su casa una noche, se encuentran con un enemigo conocido de la época de SAO y Kazuto cae fatalmente herido en la lucha y pierde el conocimiento. Cuando despierta, descubre que se ha sumergido por completo en el Inframundo, aparentemente sin forma de escapar. Se embarca entonces en la búsqueda de un camino de regreso al mundo físico una vez más.</es_ES>
        <zh_Hans>“这里……是哪儿……”
察觉到的时候，桐人不知为什么陷入了庞大的幻想风格虚拟世界。登录前的记忆模糊不清，只得在周围徘徊寻找线索。
之后，来到漆黑的巨树“基家斯西达”旁边的他，同一名少年相遇了。“我的名字是尤吉欧。请多关照，桐人君。”少年是在虚拟世界的居民――即“NPC”，但是却如同人类一样拥有“丰富感情”。
在和尤吉欧加深交往的同时，桐人也在摸索着登出这个世界的方法。在桐人的脑海中，某一个记忆苏醒了。那是幼年时的桐人和尤吉欧在山野奔跑的记忆――原本，不可能存在的记忆。而在那个回忆中，除了尤吉欧还有一个金发少女的身影。她的名字，是爱丽丝。绝对不应该忘记的、重要的名字。</zh_Hans>
        <zh_Hant>「這裡……是哪兒……」
察覺到的時候，桐人不知為什麼陷入了龐大的幻想風格虛擬世界。登錄前的記憶模糊不清，只得在周圍徘徊尋找線索。
之後，來到漆黑的巨樹「基家斯西達」旁邊的他，同一名少年相遇了。「我的名字是尤吉歐。請多關照，桐人君。」少年是在虛擬世界的居民──即「NPC」，但是卻如同人類一樣擁有「豐富感情」。
在和尤吉歐加深交往的同時，桐人也在摸索著登出這個世界的方法。在桐人的腦海中，某一個記憶蘇醒了。那是幼年時的桐人和尤吉歐在山野奔跑的記憶──原本，不可能存在的記憶。而在那個回憶中，除了尤吉歐還有一個金發少女的身影。她的名字，是愛麗絲。絕對不應該忘記的、重要的名字。</zh_Hant>
        <vi_VN>Kirito tỉnh dậy trong một khu rừng rộng lớn, hoang sơ đầy những cây cổ thụ cao lớn.
Trong cuộc tìm kiếm manh mối về sự thật xung quanh, anh gặp một cậu bé và hình như cậu ấy quen biết anh.
Khi họ tìm kiếm cha mẹ của cậu bé, một ký ức bất chợt trở lại trong tâm trí của Kirito. Đó là câu chuyện về thời thơ ấu của Kirito, cậu bé ấy và một cô gái với cái tên đáng ra không được bao giờ quên - Alice.</vi_VN>
    </synopsis>
    <information>
        <synonyms>
            <en_Latn>Sword Art Online III</en_Latn>
            <en_Latn>SAO Alicization</en_Latn>
            <en_Latn>SAO III</en_Latn>
            <en_Latn>SAO3</en_Latn>
            <en_Latn>Alicization</en_Latn>
            <en_Latn>Sōdo Āto Onrain</en_Latn>
            <ar_001 />
            <id_ID />
            <en_US />
            <ja_JP />
            <de_DE />
            <ko_KR />
            <fr_FR />
            <pt_PT />
            <ru_RU>Sword Art Online — Алисизация</ru_RU>
            <ru_RU>Искусство Меча Онлайн: Алисизация</ru_RU>
            <es_ES />
            <zh_Hans>刀剑神域 Alicization篇</zh_Hans>
            <zh_Hans>刀剑神域3</zh_Hans>
            <zh_Hant>刀劍神域 Alicization</zh_Hant>
            <zh_Hant>刀劍神域3</zh_Hant>
            <vi_VN />
        </synonyms>
        <type>
            <en_US>TV</en_US>
            <id_ID>Serial TV</id_ID>
        </type>
        <status>
            <en_US>Aired</en_US>
            <id_ID>Ditayangkan</id_ID>
        </status>
        <serialGenre>
            <en_US>Action</en_US>
            <en_US>Adventure</en_US>
            <en_US>Fantasy</en_US>
            <en_US>Romance</en_US>
            <en_US>Science Fiction</en_US>
            <en_US>Drama</en_US>
            <en_US>Mature</en_US>
            <id_ID>Aksi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Petualangan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Fantasi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Romansa</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Fiksi Ilmiah</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Drama</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Dewasa</id_ID>
        </serialGenre>
        <serialTags>
            <en_US>Game</en_US>
            <en_US>Virtual World</en_US>
            <en_US>Swordplay</en_US>
            <en_US>Artificial Intelligence</en_US>
            <en_US>Time Manipulation</en_US>
            <en_US>Video Games</en_US>
            <en_US>Isekai</en_US>
            <en_US>Dragons</en_US>
            <en_US>Tragedy</en_US>
            <en_US>Memory Manipulation</en_US>
            <en_US>Medieval</en_US>
            <en_US>RPG</en_US>
            <en_US>Virtual Reality</en_US>
            <en_US>School Life</en_US>
            <en_US>Angst</en_US>
            <en_US>Sexual Abuse</en_US>
            <en_US>Ecchi</en_US>
            <en_US>Love Polygon</en_US>
            <id_ID>Permainan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Dunia virtual</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Permainan anggar</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Kecerdasan Buatan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Manipulasi Waktu</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Video Game</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Isekai</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Naga</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Tragedi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Manipulasi Memori</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Pertengahan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>RPG</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Realitas Maya</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Kehidupan Sekolah</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Kecemasan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Pelecehan Seksual</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Ecchi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Cinta Segitiga</id_ID>
        </serialTags>
        <releaseSeason>
            <en_US>Fall</en_US>
            <id_ID>Gugur</id_ID>
            <ja_JP>秋</ja_JP>
            <ko_KR>가을</ko_KR>
            <zh_Hans>秋天</zh_Hans>
            <zh_Hant>秋天</zh_Hant>
        </releaseSeason>
        <releaseYear>2018</releaseYear>
        <episode>24</episode>
        <releaseDate>2018-10-07</releaseDate>
        <endDate>2019-03-31</endDate>
        <duration>25</duration>
        <totalDuration>625</totalDuration>
        <studio>A-1 Pictures</studio>
        <rating>PG13+</rating>
        <isNsfw>false</isNsfw>
        <adaptation>
            <en_US>Novel</en_US>
            <id_ID>Novel</id_ID>
        </adaptation>
        <country>
            <en_US>Japan</en_US>
            <id_ID>Jepang</id_ID>
        </country>
        <officialWebsite>http://www.swordart-online.net/alicization/</officialWebsite>
        <promotionalVideos>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eqp1vwV8usU</promotionalVideos>
        <promotionalVideos>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AgUDAN_6nOE</promotionalVideos>
        <producers>Aniplex</producers>
        <producers>Genco</producers>
        <producers>Bandai Namco Entertainment</producers>
        <producers>Egg Firm</producers>
        <producers>Straight Edge</producers>
        <producers>Kadokawa</producers>
        <producers>Sonilude</producers>
    </information>
    <scores>
        <aniDB>
            <id>13493</id>
            <score>5.93</score>
        </aniDB>
        <AniList>
            <id>100182</id>
            <score>75</score>
        </AniList>
        <AnimePlanet>
            <url>https://www.anime-planet.com/anime/sword-art-online-alicization</url>
            <id>9199</id>
            <score>4.142</score>
        </AnimePlanet>
        <ANN>
            <id>20665</id>
            <score>7.533</score>
        </ANN>
        <aniSearch>
            <url>https://www.anisearch.com/anime/12852,sword-art-online-alicization</url>
            <id>12852</id>
            <score>79</score>
        </aniSearch>
        <Annict>
            <id>5550</id>
            <score>92.18</score>
        </Annict>
        <IMDb>
            <code>tt2250192</code>
            <score>7.6</score>
        </IMDb>
        <KinoPoisk>
            <id>691223</id>
            <score>8.015</score>
        </KinoPoisk>
        <Kitsu>
            <slug>sword-art-online-alicization</slug>
            <id>13893</id>
            <score>79.01</score>
        </Kitsu>
        <LiveChart>
            <id>2908</id>
            <score>8.35</score>
        </LiveChart>
        <MyAnimeList>
            <id>36474</id>
            <score>7.61</score>
        </MyAnimeList>
        <MyShows>
            <id>25619</id>
            <score>4.2</score>
        </MyShows>
        <Nautiljon>
            <url>https://www.nautiljon.com/animes/sword+art+online+-+alicization.html</url>
            <score>8.52</score>
        </Nautiljon>
        <Notify>
            <base64>GWyShKmiR</base64>
            <score>7.67</score>
        </Notify>
        <OtakOtaku>
            <id>941</id>
            <score>8.82</score>
        </OtakOtaku>
        <Shikimori>
            <id>36474</id>
            <moved>true</moved>
            <newId>z36474</newId>
            <score>7.61</score>
        </Shikimori>
        <SIMKL>
            <id>724317</id>
            <score>7.8</score>
        </SIMKL>
        <TMDB>
            <url>https://www.themoviedb.org/tv/45782</url>
            <id>45782</id>
            <score>80</score>
        </TMDB>
        <Trakt>
            <url>https://trakt.tv/shows/sword-art-online</url>
            <id>45529</id>
            <score>80</score>
        </Trakt>
        <TVTime>
            <id>259640</id>
            <score>9.58</score>
        </TVTime>
    </scores>
    <updatedDate>2020-08-01T19:50:12+07:00</updatedDate>
    <streamLinks>
        <Abematv>https://abema.tv/search?q=%E3%82%BD%E3%83%BC%E3%83%89%E3%82%A2%E3%83%BC%E3%83%88%E3%83%BB%E3%82%AA%E3%83%B3%E3%83%A9%E3%82%A4%E3%83%B3%20%E3%82%A2%E3%83%AA%E3%82%B7%E3%82%BC%E3%83%BC%E3%82%B7%E3%83%A7%E3%83%B3</Abematv>
        <AdultSwim />
        <AISPlay />
        <All4 />
        <AniMe />
        <AnimeDigitalNetwork />
        <AnimeLab>https://www.animelab.com/shows/sword-art-online</AnimeLab>
        <AnimeLog />
        <AnimeOnDemand />
        <AnimePlanet />
        <animeteleto />
        <AniOne />
        <ANIPLUS>http://www.aniplustv.com/#/tv/program_view.asp?contentSerial=2086</ANIPLUS>
        <AniPlusAsia />
        <AsianCrush />
        <BahamutAnimeCrazy>https://ani.gamer.com.tw/animeVideo.php?sn=10849</BahamutAnimeCrazy>
        <BandaiChannel />
        <BandaiSpirits />
        <bilibili>https://www.bilibili.com/bangumi/media/md130412</bilibili>
        <Coalise />
        <ComicFestaAnimeZone />
        <ConTV />
        <Coolmic />
        <Crunchyroll>https://www.crunchyroll.com/sword-art-online</Crunchyroll>
        <dAnimeStore />
        <DMM />
        <FOD>http://fod.fujitv.co.jp/s/genre/anime/ser5773</FOD>
        <Funimation>https://www.funimation.com/shows/sword-art-online/</Funimation>
        <Genflix />
        <GundamInfo />
        <Gyao />
        <HIDIVE>https://www.hidive.com/tv/sword-art-online-alicization</HIDIVE>
        <Hulu>https://www.hulu.com/series/sword-art-online-alicization-c22224e3-93c0-40ab-895d-1475d94a6688</Hulu>
        <iflix />
        <iQIYI>http://www.iqiyi.com/a_19rrh1temd.html</iQIYI>
        <JapaneseAnimatedFilmClassic />
        <Mangas />
        <MBSDougaizm />
        <MidnightPulp />
        <MuseAsia>
            <en_001 />
            <vi_VN />
            <ms_MY />
            <th_TH />
            <zh_Hant_HK />
            <zh_Hant_TW />
        </MuseAsia>
        <Netflix>https://www.netflix.com/title/81029064</Netflix>
        <NicoNico>http://ch.nicovideo.jp/sao-alicization</NicoNico>
        <PrimeVideo>https://www.amazon.co.jp/dp/B07J5RJ3ZW</PrimeVideo>
        <RetroCrush />
        <SelectaVision />
        <Sushiroll />
        <Telasa />
        <TencentVideo />
        <TVNOW />
        <Vimeo />
        <VIZ />
        <VRV>https://vrv.co/series/GR49G9VP6</VRV>
        <VVVVID>https://www.vvvvid.it/show/845/sword-art-online-alicization</VVVVID>
        <Wakanim>
            <fr>https://www.wakanim.tv/fr/v2/catalogue/show/376</fr>
            <sc>https://www.wakanim.tv/sc/v2/catalogue/show/377</sc>
            <de>https://www.wakanim.tv/de/v2/catalogue/show/379</de>
            <ru>https://www.wakanim.tv/ru/v2/catalogue/show/378</ru>
        </Wakanim>
        <WeTV />
        <YamatoAnimation />
        <YouTube>
            <link />
            <isChannel>false</isChannel>
        </YouTube>
    </streamLinks>
    <signature>
        <name>Yae</name>
        <username>@Yae-chan</username>
        <discordId>481037097055027200</discordId>
        <submissionDateTime>2020-08-01T20:12:21+07:00</submissionDateTime>
        <sign>Dibantu oleh Natsu Tadama (384089845527478272)</sign>
    </signature>
</ryuuganime>