<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ryuuganime>
    <title>
        <native>君の膵臓をたべたい</native>
        <en_Latn>Kimi no Suizou wo Tabetai</en_Latn>
        <ar_001>اريد اكل بنكرياسك</ar_001>
        <id_ID>Aku Ingin Makan Pankreasmu</id_ID>
        <it_IT>Voglio mangiare il tuo pancreas</it_IT>
        <en_US>I want to eat your pancreas</en_US>
        <ja_JP>君の膵臓をたべたい</ja_JP>
        <de_DE>I want to eat your pancreas</de_DE>
        <ko_KR>너의 췌장을 먹고싶어</ko_KR>
        <fr_FR>Je veux manger ton pancréas</fr_FR>
        <pt_PT>Eu Quero Comer o Teu Pâncreas</pt_PT>
        <ru_RU>Я хочу съесть твою поджелудочную</ru_RU>
        <es_ES>Quiero comerme tu páncreas</es_ES>
        <zh_Hans>我想吃掉你的胰脏</zh_Hans>
        <zh_Hant>我想吃掉你的胰臟</zh_Hant>
        <vi_VN>Tớ Muốn Ăn Tụy Của Cậu</vi_VN>
    </title>
    <backdrop>https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/movies/16877/backgrounds/16877.jpg</backdrop>
    <visualKey>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aUxbkULgC3fpdwbdiuqKJLyfr4R.jpg</visualKey>
    <synopsis>
        <ar_001>تدور احداث هذا الفيلم حول فتى منعزل يحب قراءة الكتب , ذات يوم وبينما بطلنا يوجد في المستشفى وجد مذكرة على الارض تحمل عنوان التعايش مع الموت وتعود هذه المذكرة لساكورا ياماوتشي ذات الشعبية الكبيرة حيث كانت هذه الاخيرة تخفي اصابتها بمرض اوقف عمل البنكرياس وجعلها تنتظر الموت . .........تابعوا الفيلم لمعرفة المزيد</ar_001>
        <id_ID>Suatu hari, seorang murid SMA menemukan sebuah buku di rumah sakit berjudul "Jurnal Penyakit Koeksistensi". Itu adalah buku harian milik teman kelasnya, Sakura Yamauchi yang ditulis secara diam-diam. Ini adalah kisah seorang gadis yang menderita penyakit dan harus menghadapi kenyataan hidup yang kejam...</id_ID>
        <it_IT>Uno studente delle superiori trova per caso il diario di una compagna di classe, Sakura Yamauchi. Ma quel diario custodisce un segreto perché Sakura soffre di una gravissima malattia pancreatica. Nonostante i due abbiano personalità agli antipodi, quel tremendo segreto li avvicinerà sempre più.</it_IT>
        <en_US>The aloof protagonist: a bookworm who is deeply detached from the world he resides in. He has no interest in others and is firmly convinced that nobody has any interest in him either. His story begins when he stumbles across a handwritten book, titled "Living with Dying." He soon identifies it as a secret diary belonging to his popular, bubbly classmate Sakura Yamauchi. She then confides in him about the pancreatic disease she is suffering from and that her time left is finite. Only her family knows about her terminal illness; not even her best friends are aware. Despite this revelation, he shows zero sympathy for her plight, but caught in the waves of Sakura's persistent buoyancy, he eventually concedes to accompanying her for her remaining days.

As the pair of polar opposites interact, their connection strengthens, interweaving through their choices made with each passing day. Her apparent nonchalance and unpredictability disrupts the protagonist's impassive flow of life, gradually opening his heart as he discovers and embraces the true meaning of living.</en_US>
        <ja_JP>「君の膵臓をたべたい」……主人公である「僕」が病院で偶然拾った1冊の「共病文庫」というタイトルの文庫本。それは「僕」のクラスメイトである山内桜良（やまうち さくら）が綴っていた秘密の日記帳であり、彼女の余命が膵臓の病気により、もう長くはないことが記されていた。「僕」はその本の中身を興味本位で覗いたことにより、身内以外で唯一桜良の病気を知る人物となる。

「山内桜良の死ぬ前にやりたいこと」に付き合うことにより、「僕」、桜良という正反対の性格の2人が、互いに自分には欠けている部分にそれぞれ憧れを持ち、次第に心を通わせていきながら成長していく。そして「僕」は「人を認める人間に、人を愛する人間になること」を決意。桜良は、恋人や友人を必要としない「僕」が、初めて関わり合いを持ちたい人に自分を選んでくれたことにより「初めて私自身として必要とされている、初めて私が、たった一人の私であると思えた」と感じていく。

しかし、余命を全うすることなく、4週間の入院治療から解放されたその日に桜良は通り魔に刺されて亡くなってしまう。</ja_JP>
        <de_DE>Haruki Shiga ist ein unsozialer Einzelgänger, der seine Zeit lieber mit Büchern verbringt und in seiner Klasse kein besonders hohes Ansehen genießt. Sakura Yamauchi ist lebensfroh und charakterstark und mit ihrer offenen und sonnigen Persönlichkeit allseits beliebt. Die beiden könnten unterschiedlicher kaum sein und doch werden sie eines Tages unzertrennlich miteinander verbunden. Als Haruki im Krankenhaus darauf wartet, dass er aufgerufen wird, findet er ein kleines Buch – »Leben mit dem Tod« –, ein Tagebuch, dass das tägliche Leben eines sterbenden Menschen beschreibt. Es dauert nicht lang, bis die Besitzerin des Buches auftaucht: seine Klassenkameradin Sakura. Sakura leidet an einer Bauchspeicheldrüsenerkrankung und obwohl medizinische Fortschritte ihr ein fast normales Leben ermöglichen, wird sie bald sterben. Das ist allerdings etwas, das sie all ihren Freunden bisher verheimlicht hat, denn was sie in dieser letzten Zeit auf Erden braucht, ist kein Mitleid, sondern echte Normalität – Normalität, die sie in Haruki findet, der nun von einem »einfachen Klassenkameraden« zu einem »Klassenkameraden, der mein Geheimnis kennt« wird.

So wird Haruki von Sakura mitgerissen und umso mehr Zeit die beiden miteinander verbringen, umso mehr finden sie sich gefangen in einem Sturm aus Gefühlen, die sie sich selbst nicht erklären können. »Freundschaft«? »Liebe«? Derart triviale Worte reichen nicht, um die Beziehung der beiden zu beschreiben. »Lass uns die Welt genießen, bis ich sterbe, okay?« – das sind ihre Worte und so bricht der Freigeist Sakura Stück für Stück Harukis harte Schale und er beginnt die Welt mit anderen Augen zu sehen …</de_DE>
        <ko_KR>먼지 뿌연 도서실, 낡은 책장에 꽂힌 서적들의 순번, 조용히 책을 읽으며 생각에 잠기는 걸 좋아하는 ‘나’는 익숙한 것에서만 위안을 찾는 평범한 고등학생이다. 무료한 일상을 보내던 나는 병원에서 낡은 소파 구석에 놓인 공책 한 권을 발견한다. ‘췌장⋯⋯ 죽는다⋯⋯ 공병(共病)문고?’ 호기심을 불러일으키는 단어에 마음을 빼앗긴 내 앞에 예쁘고 명랑한 사쿠라가 나타나 공책이 자신의 것이라고 말한다. 당황한 나, 그리고 환한 미소를 짓는 사쿠라. 그녀와 나는 점점 비밀을 공유하는 친구 그 이상의 관계로 맺어지기 시작하는데⋯⋯</ko_KR>
        <fr_FR>Shiga est un lycéen introverti qui ne semble trouver du réconfort que dans la littérature. Sa vie monotone bascule le jour où, en se rendant à l'hôpital, il découvre dans la salle d'attente le journal intime de Yamauchi Sakura, sa camarade de classe. Cette dernière lui révèle alors qu'elle est atteinte d'une rare déficience du pancréas et que ses jours sont comptés.

Etant la seule personne du lycée au courant pour la maladie de la jeune fille, Shiga décide de garder le secret et d'en rester là avec elle. Mais sans qu'il ne s'en rende compte, Sakura et lui multiplient le temps passé ensemble ; et bien que leurs personnalités soient comme le jour et la nuit, chacun trouve en l'autre un précieux soutien. Ainsi Shiga décide de s'ouvrir à elle pour l'accompagner dans ses derniers jours.</fr_FR>
        <pt_PT>O diário pertence à sua colega de classe, uma menina chamada Sakura Yamauchi, que revela estar a sofrer de uma doença terminal no seu pâncreas e que só tem alguns meses para viver. Sakura explica que o protagonista é a única pessoa além da sua família que conhece a sua condição. O protagonista promete manter o segredo de Sakura. Apesar das suas personalidades completamente opostas, o protagonista decide estar junto de Sakura durante os seus últimos meses.</pt_PT>
        <ru_RU>Одним прекрасным днём ученик старшей школы находит чей-то личный дневник, подписанный как «Дневник болезни». Вскоре выясняется, что дневник этот принадлежит Сакуре Ямаути, однокласснице главного героя. Прочтя его, Харуки Сига узнаёт, что девушка страдает смертельной болезнью — её поджелудочная железа перестала работать. Чтобы поддержать её в этой нелёгкой ситуации, юноша решает подружиться с Сакурой, несмотря на их совершенно разные характеры.</ru_RU>
        <es_ES>El compañero de clases simplón es un chico que no destaca en nada, no se relaciona con nadie. Sólo esta interesado en el mundo que le muestran los libros que lee, hasta que va al hospital debido a que fue sometido a una operación de apéndice, por lo que ahora va a un chequeo de rutina.

Mientras espera, encuentra un libro titulado “Libro de convivencia con una enfermedad”. Lo comienza a leer y parece que es el diario de alguna persona que sufre de cáncer de páncreas y probablemente le quede muy poco tiempo de vida. Después de leer, una chica aparece diciendo "eso es mío" y no es nada más y nada menos que Sakura Yamauchi, la chica más popular de su clase. Así, se convierte en el compañero de clases que sabe su secreto y la acompañará hasta el día de su muerte.</es_ES>
        <zh_Hans>“没有名字的我，没有未来的她”
对他人毫无兴趣，总是独自一人读书的高中生“我”。这样的“我”有一天，偶然捡到一册写着《共病文库》的文库本。那是，天真烂漫的班上人气王·山内樱良私下记录的日记本。里面记载着她身患胰脏的疾病，已经时日无多……。
隐藏自己的疾病度过日常的樱良，与知晓其秘密的“我”。
——两人的距离，还没有名字。</zh_Hans>
        <zh_Hant>沒有名字的少年主角和沒有未來的患者女主角，他在撿到她的日記《共病文庫》後，在班上原沒有交集的兩人，生命自此有了改變。對少年來說，他想要患有胰臟疾病的少女恢復健康，對少女來說，她想要正常的人生與他一起活著。個性相反的兩人相遇後，情感得到互補。</zh_Hant>
        <vi_VN>Câu chuyện trong tiểu thuyết kể dưới góc nhìn của một nhân vật chính giấu tên. Ngày nọ, cậu tìm được một cuốn nhật ký trong bệnh viện. Quyến nhật ký này là của cô bạn cùng lớp Sakura Yamauchi của cậu, và qua đó cậu biết được rằng cô bạn của mình đang trải qua căn bệnh tuyến tụy giai đoạn cuối và chỉ còn sống được vài tháng mà thôi. Sakura đã nói rằng cậu là người duy nhất ngoài gia đình cô biết về sự thật này. Cậu đã hứa giữ bí mật cho Sakura. Dù tính cách của họ hoàn toàn trái ngược nhau, nhân vật chính quyết định sẽ ở bên cạnh Sakura trong những ngày tháng cuối đời của cô.</vi_VN>
    </synopsis>
    <information>
        <synonyms>
            <en_Latn>KimiSui</en_Latn>
            <en_Latn>Kimi no Suizō wo Tabetai</en_Latn>
            <ar_001 />
            <hu_HU />
            <he_IL />
            <id_ID />
            <en_US>Let Me Eat Your Pancreas</en_US>
            <ja_JP />
            <de_DE />
            <ko_KR />
            <fr_FR />
            <pt_PT />
            <ru_RU>Хочу съесть твою поджелудочную железу</ru_RU>
            <es_ES>Vull menjar-me el teu pàncrees</es_ES>
            <zh_Hans />
            <zh_Hant />
            <vi_VN />
        </synonyms>
        <type>
            <en_US>Movie</en_US>
            <id_ID>Film</id_ID>
        </type>
        <status>
            <en_US>Aired</en_US>
            <id_ID>Ditayangkan</id_ID>
        </status>
        <serialGenre>
            <en_US>Drama</en_US>
            <en_US>Romance</en_US>
            <en_US>Slice of Life</en_US>
            <id_ID>Drama</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Romansa</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Potongan Kehidupan</id_ID>
        </serialGenre>
        <serialTags>
            <en_US>Seinen</en_US>
            <en_US>Illness</en_US>
            <en_US>School Life</en_US>
            <en_US>Tragedy</en_US>
            <en_US>Philosophy</en_US>
            <en_US>School</en_US>
            <en_US>Slow When It Comes To Love</en_US>
            <id_ID>Seinen</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Penyakit</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Kehidupan Sekolah</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Tragedi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Filosofi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Sekolah</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Lamban Saat Mencintai</id_ID>
        </serialTags>
        <releaseSeason>
            <en_US>Summer</en_US>
            <id_ID>Panas</id_ID>
            <ja_JP>夏</ja_JP>
            <ko_KR>여름</ko_KR>
            <zh_Hans>夏天</zh_Hans>
            <zh_Hant>夏天</zh_Hant>
        </releaseSeason>
        <releaseYear>2018</releaseYear>
        <episode>1</episode>
        <releaseDate>2018-09-01</releaseDate>
        <endDate>2018-09-01</endDate>
        <duration>108</duration>
        <totalDuration>108</totalDuration>
        <studio>Studio VOLN</studio>
        <rating>PG13+</rating>
        <isNsfw>false</isNsfw>
        <adaptation>
            <en_US>Novel</en_US>
            <id_ID>Novel</id_ID>
        </adaptation>
        <country>
            <en_US>Japan</en_US>
            <id_ID>Jepang</id_ID>
        </country>
    </information>
    <scores>
        <aniDB>
            <id>13363</id>
            <score>8.12</score>
        </aniDB>
        <AniList>
            <id>99750</id>
            <score>83</score>
        </AniList>
        <AnimePlanet>
            <url>https://www.anime-planet.com/anime/i-want-to-eat-your-pancreas</url>
            <id>9068</id>
            <score>4.534</score>
        </AnimePlanet>
        <ANN>
            <id>20388</id>
            <score>8.065</score>
        </ANN>
        <aniSearch>
            <url>https://www.anisearch.com/anime/12730,kimi-no-suizou-o-tabetai</url>
            <id>12730</id>
            <score>88</score>
        </aniSearch>
        <Annict>
            <id>5401</id>
            <score />
        </Annict>
        <IMDb>
            <code>tt7236034</code>
            <score>7.9</score>
        </IMDb>
        <KinoPoisk>
            <id>1048908</id>
            <score>7.751</score>
        </KinoPoisk>
        <Kitsu>
            <slug>kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai</slug>
            <id>13723</id>
            <score>82.56</score>
        </Kitsu>
        <LiveChart>
            <id>2829</id>
            <score>8.94</score>
        </LiveChart>
        <MyAnimeList>
            <id>36098</id>
            <score>8.6</score>
        </MyAnimeList>
        <MyShows>
            <id />
            <score />
        </MyShows>
        <Nautiljon>
            <url>https://www.nautiljon.com/animes/kimi+no+suizo+wo+tabetai.html</url>
            <score>9.24</score>
        </Nautiljon>
        <Notify>
            <base64>3RRI2FiiR</base64>
            <score>8.67</score>
        </Notify>
        <OtakOtaku>
            <id>1047</id>
            <score>9.71</score>
        </OtakOtaku>
        <Shikimori>
            <id>36098</id>
            <moved>true</moved>
            <newID>z36098</newID>
            <score>8.6</score>
        </Shikimori>
        <SIMKL>
            <id>708497</id>
            <score>8.6</score>
        </SIMKL>
        <TMDB>
            <url>https://www.themoviedb.org/movie/504253</url>
            <id>504253</id>
            <score>82</score>
        </TMDB>
        <Trakt>
            <url>https://trakt.tv/movies/i-want-to-eat-your-pancreas-2018</url>
            <id>351528</id>
            <score>82</score>
        </Trakt>
        <TVTime>
            <id>16877</id>
            <score />
        </TVTime>
    </scores>
    <updatedDate>2020-05-25T02:16:16+07:00</updatedDate>
    <fansub>
        <idn>
            <Aibou />
            <Aizukara />
            <Allsub />
            <Alter />
            <AnimeGokil />
            <AniToki>http://anitoki.web.id/2018/12/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai-subtitle-indonesia/</AniToki>
            <AoiTenshi />
            <Arks />
            <ASubs />
            <AWSubs>https://awsubs.co/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai-i-want-to-eat-your-pancreas-subtitle-indonesia/</AWSubs>
            <Bentoo />
            <Caramel />
            <Cijanepoi />
            <Conan />
            <DAnimeSubs />
            <Del />
            <DNFI />
            <Durandal />
            <EmotPekmen />
            <Excalibur />
            <Gantz />
            <Gin />
            <Haruna />
            <Haruzora />
            <HunterNoSekai />
            <IA />
            <Inazumaotoshi />
            <Indis />
            <Inform0930 />
            <Isekai />
            <Junk />
            <Kazefuri />
            <Kinshiru />
            <KO />
            <Kopaja />
            <LCC />
            <MangaNekoTranslation />
            <Melody />
            <Mite />
            <Nanairo />
            <Neo />
            <OPLovers />
            <Ougi />
            <Panagayan />
            <Pendekar />
            <Pucuk>https://pucuktranslation.pw/film-layar-lebar-i-want-to-eat-your-pancreas/</Pucuk>
            <Quinime />
            <RevieXion />
            <Samehadaku />
            <SilverYasha />
            <Sora />
            <TTOD />
            <Vedifi />
            <Warung />
            <Wibu />
            <Yuki />
            <Zen />
        </idn>
        <eng>
            <Horrible />
        </eng>
    </fansub>
    <fanshare>
        <idn>
            <AniBatch>https://www.anibatch.me/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai-bd/</AniBatch>
            <AnimeKompi />
            <AnimeSAVE>http://www.animesave.com/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai-subtitle-indonesia/</AnimeSAVE>
            <Bakacan>https://bakacan.id/anime/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai/</Bakacan>
            <Drivenime />
            <Hinime>https://hinime.com/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai-sub-indo/</Hinime>
            <Koenime>https://www.koenime.com/kimisui-sub-indo/</Koenime>
            <Kusonime>https://kusonime.com/movie-kimisui-sub-indo/</Kusonime>
            <Mikanime>https://mikanime.com/kimi-no-suizou-bd-sub-indo/</Mikanime>
            <Moenime>https://moenime.web.id/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai-sub-indo/</Moenime>
            <Ryuukoi>https://ryuukoi.web.id/anime/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai/</Ryuukoi>
            <WibuDesu>https://wibudesu.com/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai-bd-subtitle-indonesia/</WibuDesu>
        </idn>
        <eng>
            <AnimeKayo>https://animekayo.com/?s=Kimi+no+Suizou</AnimeKayo>
        </eng>
    </fanshare>
    <fanstream>
        <idn>
            <AnimeIndoNET>http://animeindo.moe/anime/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai-2018</AnimeIndoNET>
            <anoBoy>https://anoboy.us/anime/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai/</anoBoy>
            <Gomunime>Moeclip: https://moeclip.com/anime/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai-sub-indo/</Gomunime>
            <Neonime>https://neonime.moe/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai-movie-subtitle-indonesia-2/</Neonime>
            <Onnime>OtakuIndo:</Onnime>
        </idn>
        <eng>
            <fourAnime>https://4anime.to/anime/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai</fourAnime>
            <nineAnime>https://9anime.ru/watch/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai.4myj</nineAnime>
            <AnimeDaisuki />
            <AnimeTwist>https://twist.moe/a/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai/1</AnimeTwist>
            <Animeflix />
            <AnimeHeaven>https://animeheaven.ru/detail/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai.17049</AnimeHeaven>
            <Animelon />
            <Animeultima>https://www1.animeultima.to/a/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai_194854</Animeultima>
            <AniWatch>https://aniwatch.me/anime/1020</AniWatch>
            <GogoAnime>https://gogoanimes.co/category/kimi-no-suizou-wo-tabetai</GogoAnime>
            <KissAnime>http://kissanime.ru/Anime/Kimi-no-Suizou-wo-Tabetai</KissAnime>
            <WonderfulSubs>https://beta.wonderfulsubs.com/watch/iwanttoeatyourpancreas</WonderfulSubs>
        </eng>
    </fanstream>
    <library>
        <Nyaa>https://nyaa.si/?f=0&amp;c=0_0&amp;q=Kimi+no+Suizou+wo+Tabetai</Nyaa>
        <PerpusIndo>https://www.perpusindo.info/sharelist?kat=&amp;user=&amp;cari=Kimi%20no%20Suizou%20wo%20Tabetai&amp;kartel=</PerpusIndo>
        <Shallty>https://shallty.moe/browse?search=Kimi%20no%20Suizou%20wo%20Tabetai</Shallty>
    </library>
    <signature>
        <name>Natsu Tadama</name>
        <username>@nattadasu</username>
        <discordId>384089845527478300</discordId>
        <submissionDateTime>2020-05-25T02:31:11+07:00</submissionDateTime>
        <sign>RGlnaXRhbGx5IFNpZ25lZCBieSBOYXRzdSBUYWRhbWEgQCBBY2VoLCBJbmRvbmVzaWE=</sign>
    </signature>
</ryuuganime>