<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ryuuganime id="000010" version="1.1-rv">
    <title>
        <native>さらざんまい</native>
        <en_Latn>Sarazanmai</en_Latn>
        <ar_001>سارازانماي</ar_001>
        <id_ID>Sarazanmai</id_ID>
        <en_US>Sarazanmai</en_US>
        <ja_JP>さらざんまい</ja_JP>
        <de_DE>Sarazanmai</de_DE>
        <ko_KR>사라잔마이</ko_KR>
        <fr_FR>Sarazanmai</fr_FR>
        <pt_PT>Sarazanmai</pt_PT>
        <ru_RU>Сарадзаммай</ru_RU>
        <es_ES>Sarazanmai</es_ES>
        <zh_Hans>皿三昧</zh_Hans>
        <zh_Hant>皿三昧</zh_Hant>
        <vi_VN>Sarazanmai</vi_VN>
    </title>
    <backdrop>https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/fanart/original/5c83e7ceef84f.jpg</backdrop>
    <visualKey>https://artworks.thetvdb.com/banners/posters/5c83e72ce92c5.jpg</visualKey>
    <synopsis>
        <ar_001>“كازوكي ياساكا”، طالب في الصف الثامن يعيش في “اساكوسا”، يتحول إلى وحش كابا إضافة إلى زملائه في الفصل “توي” و”انتا” بواسطة مخلوق غامض يدعى “كابي” بعد أن كسروا تمثالًا لكابا، إله يحمي المدينة.</ar_001>
        <id_ID>Suatu hari, tiga siswa SMA kelas dua; Kazuki Yasaka, Toi Kuji, dan Enta Jinai bertemu dengan kappa bernama Keppi, yang merupakan pewaris takhta Kerajaan Kappa. Keppi terpaksa mengambil paksa shirikodama mereka dan mengubah mereka menjadi kappa...</id_ID>
        <en_US>After the noble Kappa Kingdom falls to the Otter Empire, the Kappa prince Keppi loses much of his power and becomes helpless against the unseen Kapa-zombies. These zombies plague the world, and are the creations of the Otters and manifestations of people's deepest desires. With no other choice, Keppi must rely on three young boys: Kazuki Yasaka, who must carry a box with him wherever he goes; Enta Jinnai, Kazuki's childhood friend; and Tooi Kuji, a delinquent and a school truant.

By having the mythical organ called a shirikodama removed from them, the boys are able to become Kappa themselves and fight the Kapa-zombies. However, to defeat them, the boys must connect with each other via their minds, bodies, and—most importantly—secrets. As the Kappa Kingdom relies on these boys, they must reveal themselves as they have never done before, all the while learning that connections are fragile and truly precious things.</en_US>
        <ja_JP>舞台は浅草。 中学2年生の矢逆一稀、久慈悠、陣内燕太の３人はある日、謎のカッパ型生命体“ケッピ”に出会い、 無理やり尻子玉を奪われカッパに変身させられてしまう。 『元の姿に戻りたければ“ある方法”でつながり、ゾンビの尻子玉を持ってこい』 ケッピにそう告げられる3人。少年たちはつながりあい、ゾンビの尻子玉を奪うことができるのか？！ 同じ頃、新星玲央と阿久津真武が勤務する交番でも 何かが起ころうとしていたー。</ja_JP>
        <de_DE>Der Original-Anime Sarazanmai entführt uns in den Tokioter Stadtteil Asakusa, wo die drei Freunde Kazuki Yasaka, Tooi Kuji und Enta Jinnai eine Kreatur namens Keppi antreffen, die sich selbst als den Thronfolger des Kappa-Königreichs ausgibt. Keppi fackelt auch nicht lang und stiehlt die Shirikodama – ein mythisches Organ, das von Kappas gestohlen werden muss, bevor sie an die Leber ihrer Opfer gelangen – der drei Mittelschüler und verwandelt sie so kurzerhand selbst in Kappas. Um wieder zu Menschen zu werden, so erklärt Keppi ihnen, müssen sie nun die Shirikodama von Zombies sammeln und zu ihm bringen. Dabei gibt er ihnen noch mit auf den Weg, dass sie sich »auf diese bestimmte Weise« miteinander verbinden müssten …

Können die drei verwandelten Jungs es schaffen, genügend Shirikodama von Zombies zu sammeln und wieder zu Menschen zu werden? &lt;br&gt;Quelle: &lt;a href="https://www.anisearch.de/anime/13435,sarazanmai"&gt;aniSearch.de&lt;/a&gt;</de_DE>
        <ko_KR>어느 날 캇파 왕국 제1 왕위계승자라 자칭하는 수수께끼의 캇파 생명체 켓피에게 시리코다마를 빼앗겨 캇파로 변해버린 중학교 2학년 남학생들의 이야기를 그린 애니메이션</ko_KR>
        <fr_FR>L’histoire se déroule à Asakusa. Kazuki Yasaka, Toi Kuji et Enta Jinnai, tous trois en 5e, font un beau jour la rencontre de Keppi, un être mystérieux à l’apparence de kappa. Ce dernier leur subtilise leur shirikodama, une boule mystique logée dans l’anus, et ils se transforment en kappa eux-mêmes. Keppi leur déclare que pour retrouver leur apparence initiale, ils devront lui rapporter le shirikodama d’un zombie. Y parviendront-ils ? Au même moment, au poste de police où travaillent Reo Niiboshi et Mabu Akutsu, quelque chose est sur le point de se produire...</fr_FR>
        <pt_PT>Um dia, em Asakusa, três estudantes do fundamental - Kazuki Yasaka, Toi Kuji e Enta Jinnai - conhecem Keppi, um misterioso kappa que rouba suas jóias místicas e os transforma em kappas. Para voltar para sua forma original, eles precisam enfrentar kappas zumbis e roubar as jóias místicas deles. Ao mesmo tempo, algo estranho está acontecendo na delegacia onde trabalham Reo Niiboshi e Mabu Akutsu. Esta é a história de três garotos que não conseguem se conectar com alguém que lhes é importante, e estão aprendendo o verdadeiro significado dessas conexões.</pt_PT>
        <ru_RU>Место действия этой истории — Асакуса, один из кварталов Токио.
Однажды трое учеников второго года средней школы — Кадзуки Ясака, Той Кудзи и Энта Дзиннай — встречают Кэппи, странное существо, очень похожее на каппу, и по совместительству самопровозглашённого наследника трона королевства Каппа. Кэппи забирает у ребят сирикодама (яп. 尻子玉, шарик из плоти, мифический орган, который каппа крадёт у людей через анус), тем самым превращая их в капп. Теперь, чтобы вернуть прежний облик, мальчики должны соединиться «неким способом» и принести Кэппи сирикодама зомби. Смогут ли ребята соединиться и забрать сирикодама у зомби? Тем временем двое полицейских, Рэо Нибоси и Мабу Акуцу, что-то замышляют в своей будке.</ru_RU>
        <es_ES>Nos encontramos en Asakusa, donde los estudiantes de segundo año de secundaria Kazuki Yasaka, Toi Kuji y Enta Jinnai conocerán a Keppi, una misteriosa criatura con aspecto de kapa que les roba la shirikodama a todos y los transforma en kappas. "Si quieren recuperar su forma original deberán luchar contra los zombis y tomar sus shirikodamas". ¿Podrán conectar los jóvenes entre sí y enfrentar a los zombis como les piden? Mientras tanto, algo ocurre en la estación de policía donde trabajan Reo Niiboshi y Mabu Akutsu.</es_ES>
        <zh_Hans>舞台是浅草。初中二年级的矢逆一稀、久慈悠、阵内燕太三人，某天遇到了神秘的河童型生命体“Keppi”，并被强行夺走了尻子玉而变成了河童。“想要变回原状的话，就通过‘某个方法’产生联系，并把僵尸的尻子玉拿来吧”。Keppi如此告知三人。究竟少年们能否相互产生联系，并夺取僵尸的尻子玉呢？！与此同时，新星玲央和阿久津真武执勤的派出所，似乎也发生了什么。</zh_Hans>
        <zh_Hant>舞台是淺草。初中二年級的矢逆一稀、久慈悠、陣內燕太三人，某天遇到了神秘的河童型生命體“Keppi”，並被強行奪走了尻子玉而變成了河童。 “想要變回原狀的話，就通過‘某個方法’產生聯系，並把僵尸的尻子玉拿來吧”。Keppi如此告知三人。究竟少年們能否相互產生聯系，並奪取僵尸的尻子玉呢？！與此同時，新星玲央和阿久津真武執勤的派出所，似乎也發生了什麼。</zh_Hant>
        <vi_VN>Một ngày nọ, ba cậu học sinh sơ trung – Kazuki Yasaka, Toi Kuji, và Enta Jinai – tình cờ gặp một sinh vật lạ có hình dáng giống kappa, tên của nó là Keppi và nó tự xưng mình là người kế thừa ngôi vị tại vương quốc Kappa. Keppi đã dùng sức mạnh của mình mà lấy đi shirikodama của ba cậu bé (theo truyền thuyết shirikodama là một bộ phận kì bí giấu trong hậu môn của mỗi người, thứ mà kappa rất thèm muốn) và cả ba cậu bé đều đã bị biến thành kappa. Keppi nói với chúng rằng: “Nếu các ngươi muốn trở lại thành người, các ngươi cần phải được kết nối bằng “cách đó” và các ngươi phải mang cho ta shirikodama của lũ thây ma.” Liệu những cậu bé ấy có thể hoàn thành nhiệm vụ và trở lại thành người không?</vi_VN>
    </synopsis>
    <information>
        <synonyms>
            <en_Latn />
            <ar_001 />
            <id_ID />
            <en_US />
            <ja_JP />
            <de_DE />
            <ko_KR />
            <fr_FR />
            <pt_PT />
            <ru_RU />
            <es_ES />
            <zh_Hans />
            <zh_Hant />
            <vi_VN />
        </synonyms>
        <type>
            <en_US>TV</en_US>
            <id_ID>Serial TV</id_ID>
        </type>
        <status>
            <en_US>Aired</en_US>
            <id_ID>Ditayangkan</id_ID>
        </status>
        <serialGenre>
            <en_US>Action</en_US>
            <en_US>Fantasy</en_US>
            <en_US>Supernatural</en_US>
            <en_US>Drama</en_US>
            <en_US>Comedy</en_US>
            <en_US>Romance</en_US>
            <en_US>Slice of Life</en_US>
            <en_US>Science Fiction</en_US>
            <en_US>Music</en_US>
            <id_ID>Aksi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Fantasi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Supernatural</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Drama</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Komedi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Romansa</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Fiksi Ilmiah</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Potongan Kehidupan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Musik</id_ID>
        </serialGenre>
        <serialTags>
            <en_US>Psychology</en_US>
            <en_US>Demon</en_US>
            <en_US>Police</en_US>
            <en_US>Surreal Comedy</en_US>
            <en_US>Youkai</en_US>
            <en_US>Musical</en_US>
            <en_US>Urban Fantasy</en_US>
            <en_US>Henshin</en_US>
            <en_US>Gender Bending</en_US>
            <en_US>Football</en_US>
            <en_US>Zombie</en_US>
            <en_US>Shounen-Ai</en_US>
            <en_US>LGBTQ Themes</en_US>
            <en_US>Crossdressing</en_US>
            <en_US>Drugs</en_US>
            <en_US>Contemporary Fantasy</en_US>
            <en_US>Japanese Mythology</en_US>
            <en_US>Middle School</en_US>
            <en_US>Guns</en_US>
            <en_US>Slapstic</en_US>
            <en_US>Amnesia</en_US>
            <en_US>Questionnable Content</en_US>
            <en_US>Violence</en_US>
            <id_ID>Psikologis</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Iblis</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Polisi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Komedi Ganjil</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Youkai</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Musikal</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Fantasi Urban</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Henshin</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Perubahan Gender</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Sepak Bola</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Zombi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Percintaan Lelaki</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Tema LGBTQ</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Crossdress</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Narkoba</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Fantasi Kontemporer</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Mitologi Jepang</id_ID>
            <id_ID>SMP</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Senapan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Dagelan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Amnesia</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Konten yang Perlu Dipertanyakan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Kekerasan</id_ID>
        </serialTags>
        <releaseSeason>
            <en_US>Spring</en_US>
            <id_ID>Semi</id_ID>
            <ja_JP>春</ja_JP>
            <ko_KR>봄</ko_KR>
            <zh_Hans>春天</zh_Hans>
            <zh_Hant>春天</zh_Hant>
        </releaseSeason>
        <releaseYear>2019</releaseYear>
        <episode>11</episode>
        <releaseDate>2019-04-12</releaseDate>
        <endDate>2019-06-21</endDate>
        <duration>23</duration>
        <totalDuration>253</totalDuration>
        <studio>MAPPA</studio>
        <studio>Lapin Track</studio>
        <rating>PG13+</rating>
        <isNsfw>true</isNsfw>
        <adaptation>
            <en_US>Original</en_US>
            <id_ID>Orisinal</id_ID>
        </adaptation>
        <country>
            <en_US>Japan</en_US>
            <id_ID>Jepang</id_ID>
        </country>
        <officialWebsite>http://sarazanmai.com/</officialWebsite>
        <promotionalVideos>https://youtu.be/SmjKRnEyai0</promotionalVideos>
        <producers>Aniplex</producers>
        <producers>Dentsu</producers>
        <producers>Movic</producers>
        <producers>Fuji TV</producers>
        <producers>Gentosha Comics</producers>
    </information>
    <scores>
        <aniDB>
            <id>13869</id>
            <score>5.65</score>
        </aniDB>
        <AniList>
            <id>101261</id>
            <score>74</score>
        </AniList>
        <AnimePlanet>
            <url>https://www.anime-planet.com/anime/sarazanmai</url>
            <id>9796</id>
            <score>3.918</score>
        </AnimePlanet>
        <ANN>
            <id>21544</id>
            <score>7.247</score>
        </ANN>
        <aniSearch>
            <url>https://www.anisearch.com/anime/13435,sarazanmai</url>
            <id>13435</id>
            <score>62</score>
        </aniSearch>
        <Annict>
            <id>5780</id>
            <score>92.41</score>
        </Annict>
        <IMDb>
            <code>tt8096510</code>
            <score>7</score>
        </IMDb>
        <KinoPoisk>
            <id>1208412</id>
            <score />
        </KinoPoisk>
        <Kitsu>
            <slug>sarazanmai</slug>
            <id>41017</id>
            <score>76.04</score>
        </Kitsu>
        <LiveChart>
            <id>3127</id>
            <score>7.66</score>
        </LiveChart>
        <MyAnimeList>
            <id>37426</id>
            <score>7.59</score>
        </MyAnimeList>
        <MyShows>
            <id>61181</id>
            <score>4.12</score>
        </MyShows>
        <Nautiljon>
            <url>https://www.nautiljon.com/animes/sarazanmai.html</url>
            <score>7.96</score>
        </Nautiljon>
        <Notify>
            <base64>SJed2FiiR</base64>
            <score>7.11</score>
        </Notify>
        <OtakOtaku>
            <id>1372</id>
            <score>5</score>
        </OtakOtaku>
        <Shikimori>
            <id>37426</id>
            <score>7.59</score>
        </Shikimori>
        <SIMKL>
            <id>776633</id>
            <score>7.2</score>
        </SIMKL>
        <TMDB>
            <url>https://www.themoviedb.org/tv/86919-sarazanmai</url>
            <id>86919</id>
            <score>83</score>
        </TMDB>
        <Trakt>
            <url>https://trakt.tv/shows/sarazanmai</url>
            <id>144651</id>
            <score>71</score>
        </Trakt>
        <TVTime>
            <id>357047</id>
            <score>9.62</score>
        </TVTime>
    </scores>
    <updatedDate>2020-07-31T01:09:18+07:00</updatedDate>
    <streamLinks>
        <Abematv />
        <AdultSwim />
        <AISPlay />
        <All4 />
        <AniMe />
        <AnimeDigitalNetwork />
        <AnimeLab>https://www.animelab.com/shows/sarazanmai</AnimeLab>
        <AnimeLog />
        <AnimeOnDemand>https://www.anime-on-demand.de/anime/335</AnimeOnDemand>
        <AnimePlanet />
        <animeteleto />
        <AniOne />
        <ANIPLUS>http://www.aniplustv.com/#/tv/program_view.asp?contentSerial=2153</ANIPLUS>
        <AniPlusAsia />
        <AsianCrush />
        <BahamutAnimeCrazy />
        <BandaiChannel />
        <BandaiSpirits />
        <bilibili>https://www.bilibili.com/bangumi/media/md22718857</bilibili>
        <Coalise />
        <ComicFestaAnimeZone />
        <ConTV />
        <Coolmic />
        <Crunchyroll>https://www.crunchyroll.com/sarazanmai</Crunchyroll>
        <dAnimeStore />
        <DMM />
        <FOD />
        <Funimation>https://www.funimation.com/shows/sarazanmai/</Funimation>
        <Genflix />
        <GundamInfo />
        <Gyao />
        <HIDIVE />
        <Hulu />
        <iflix />
        <iQIYI />
        <JapaneseAnimatedFilmClassic />
        <Mangas />
        <MBSDougaizm />
        <MidnightPulp />
        <MuseAsia>
            <en_001 />
            <vi_VN />
            <ms_MY />
            <th_TH />
            <zh_Hant_HK />
            <zh_Hant_TW />
        </MuseAsia>
        <Netflix />
        <NicoNico>http://ch.nicovideo.jp/sarazanmai-anime</NicoNico>
        <PrimeVideo />
        <RetroCrush />
        <SelectaVision />
        <Sushiroll />
        <Telasa />
        <TencentVideo />
        <TVNOW />
        <U-NEXT>http://video.unext.jp/title/SID0041072</U-NEXT>
        <VideoPass>https://www.videopass.jp/series/9533</VideoPass>
        <Vimeo />
        <VIZ />
        <VRV>https://vrv.co/series/G6G5JZ1D6</VRV>
        <VVVVID />
        <Wakanim>
            <fr>https://www.wakanim.tv/fr/v2/catalogue/show/490</fr>
            <sc />
            <de />
            <ru>https://www.wakanim.tv/ru/v2/catalogue/show/491</ru>
        </Wakanim>
        <WeTV />
        <YamatoAnimation />
        <YouTube>
            <link />
            <isChannel>false</isChannel>
        </YouTube>
    </streamLinks>
    <signature>
        <name>Natsu Tadama</name>
        <username>@nattadasu</username>
        <discordId>384089845527478300</discordId>
        <submissionDateTime>2020-07-31T01:22:13+07:00</submissionDateTime>
        <sign>RGlnaXRhbGx5IFNpZ25lZCBieSBOYXRzdSBUYWRhbWEgQCBBY2VoLCBJbmRvbmVzaWE=</sign>
    </signature>
</ryuuganime>