<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ryuuganime>
    <title>
        <native>抱かれたい男1位に脅されています。</native>
        <en_Latn>Dakaretai Otoko 1-i ni Odosarete Imasu.</en_Latn>
        <ar_001>اكثر رجل مطلوب احتضانه</ar_001>
        <id_ID>Dakaretai Otoko 1-i ni Odosarete Imasu.</id_ID>
        <en_US>Dakaichi: I'm Being Harassed by the Sexiest Man of the Year</en_US>
        <ja_JP>抱かれたい男1位に脅されています。</ja_JP>
        <de_DE>Dakaichi: My Number 1</de_DE>
        <ko_KR>안기고 싶은 남자 1위에게 협박당하고 있습니다.</ko_KR>
        <fr_FR>DAKAICHI -My number 1-</fr_FR>
        <pt_PT />
        <ru_RU>Угроза для парня №1</ru_RU>
        <es_ES />
        <zh_Hans>我让最想被拥抱的男人给威胁了。</zh_Hans>
        <zh_Hant>我讓最想被擁抱的男人給威脅了。</zh_Hant>
        <vi_VN>Dakaretai Otoko 1-i ni Odosarete Imasu.</vi_VN>
    </title>
    <backdrop>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dZ2wHYUMcswAPlAbYsoJWiXdrPc.jpg</backdrop>
    <visualKey>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1cWev0aDMQ09Y21h3o3Smp6Xdm9.jpg</visualKey>
    <synopsis>
        <ar_001>سوف أفعلها حتى أجعل جسدك غير قادر على نسيان خاصتي” حاز “سايجيو تاكاتو” على لقب “الأكثر قابلية للعناق” واشتهر لمدة خمس سنوات. حتى ظهر الممثل الجديد “أزومايا جونتا”. بالمقارنة بينهما كان “تاكاتو” دائما يعتبر فظا بينما تكتسح ابتسامة “أزومايا” المعجبين، هذا الفشل يدفع “تاكاتو” إلى الإدمان بالخمر. وأفعاله هذه تجذب انتباه “ازومايا” الذي يريد أن يراه. لدهشته، يستخدم “ازومايا” هذه المعلومات الجديدة لتهديد “تاكاتو” ليكون ودودا جسديا معه.......تابعوا الانمي لمعرفة المزيد</ar_001>
        <id_ID>Saijyo Takato telah menjadi nomor satu dalam “Lelaki Yang Ingin Orang Peluk” selama lima tahun. Namun, semenjak munculnya aktor baru Azumaya Junta. Takato selalu dibandingkan dengan senyum Azumaya yang mengalahkannya . Seluruh kegagalan tersebut mendorong Takato untuk minum sake dan tindakannya menaik perhatian orang yang ingin dia lihat. Mengejutkannya, Azumaya menggunakan info baru ini untuk memeras Takuto untuk sebuah kasih sayang.</id_ID>
        <en_US>Takato Saijou has held the title of "Sexiest Man of the Year" for five years running. He is an accomplished actor, with 20 years of experience under his belt, and is aware his good looks are well above average. Proud of his career, Takato regards the title as an appropriate indicator of his success.
But when his reign is ended by acting newbie Junta Azumaya, who debuted only three years ago, Takato's initial shock gives way to jealous hostility. Even in the new drama that he has been cast in, Junta seems to have suddenly surpassed him; snatching Takato's usual spot of lead actor, Junta continually manages to get on his nerves. Most infuriating of all are the bright smile and kind words that accompany everything Junta does.
All this animosity comes to a head, however, when Junta catches Takato in a rather vulnerable drunken state. Endangering his own public image, Takato confronts the junior actor with harsh words and angry comments—an opportunity Junta takes every advantage of. With the famous actor Takato Saijou now on video picking a fight with a co-star, Junta has the perfect means to blackmail him.
Asking the price of his enemy's silence, Takato is shocked to find that his motivation lies far from advancing his career; instead, Junta's terms are those that can only be realized in the bedroom!</en_US>
        <ja_JP>2013年7月、連載を開始した、 桜日梯子による『抱かれたい男1位に脅されています。』。 5年連続で”抱かれたい男1位”だったベテラン俳優・西條高人と、 その座を奪った新人俳優・東谷准太。 芸能界を舞台に繰り広げられる”抱かれたい男” ツートップ同士の禁断のスキャンダルを センセーショナルに描く本作は、 遂にシリーズ累計発行部数215万部を突破。 そんないま最も人気を集める ボーイズ・ラブコミックが、ファン待望のTVアニメ化。 2018年、最大のスキャンダルが 幕をあける――！</ja_JP>
        <de_DE>Takato Saijou ist seit fünf Jahren stolzer Verfechter des Titels eines der begehrtesten Männer, der Most Huggable, bis plötzlich der Neuling und Schauspieler Junta Azumaya auf der Bildfläche erscheint und ihm den Titel streitig macht. Während Takato vom Typ her eher schroff rüberkommt, fällt es Azumaya schon mit seinem strahlenden Lächeln leicht, seine Bewunderer für sich zu gewinnen. Für Takato ist das alles zu viel und er gibt sich in einem schwachen Moment dem Alkohol hin, und als er dachte, dass es schlimmer nicht hätte kommen können, passiert es: Junta erwischt ihn in seinem betrunkenen Zustand! Und dann nutzt Junta die peinliche Situation auch noch aus, um Takato zu erpressen. Als Austausch für sein Schweigen verlangt Junta nun besondere Zuneigung von Takato!</de_DE>
        <ko_KR>5년 연속으로 "안기고 싶은 남자 1위"가 된 베테랑 배우 사이죠 타카토와 그 자리를 빼앗으려는 신인 배우 아즈마야 쥰타. 예능계를 무대로 엮어나가는 "안기고 싶은 남자" 투 탑 동시 금단의 스캔들을 센세이셔널하게 그려나간다.

2018년 최대의 스캔들이 막을 연다!</ko_KR>
        <fr_FR>Saijou Takato est acteur depuis sa plus tendre enfance et élu depuis 5 ans "l'homme le plus désiré". Cependant, son règne s'arrête brutalement face à l'arrivée d'Azumaya Junta, un jeune acteur ayant débuté sa carrière 3 ans plus tôt. Takato supporte assez mal de se retrouver relégué au second rang et voit ce jeune prodige comme un ennemi.

Néanmoins, suite à une soirée trop alcoolisée, Takato se retrouve dans le lit de Junta.</fr_FR>
        <pt_PT />
        <ru_RU>Такато Сайдзё на протяжении пяти лет сохранял за собой положение лучшего актёра. Но настал тот день, когда его потеснил более молодой актёр с незначительным трёхлетним стажем. Молодой актёр обладал искренней и ослепительной улыбкой. Улыбка Дзюнты Адзумаи произвела свой эффект и на надменного и враждебно настроенного Такато.
Однажды позорно напившись во время пьянки, Сайдзё выплеснул все негативные эмоции в сторону Адзумаи. К несчастью для Сайдзё, Адзумая снимал всё это на телефон, и свой «фильм» юноша использовал для того, чтобы шантажировать его! Из-за недопонимания Такато не думая ставит Дзюнте очень смелое условие. Какие последствия это может за собой повлечь — он не знал...</ru_RU>
        <es_ES>"Haré que tu cuerpo sea incapaz de olvidar el mío". Los cinco años de reinado de Saijou Takato como el "N º 1 más abrazable" han sido arrebatados. Robándole el protagonismo es el actor novato con un debut de tres años, Azumaya! Hacia el hostil y estirado Takato, la sonrisa sincera y brillante de Azumaya comienza a hacerse efectiva. Incluso cuando Takato pone su nivel de alerta en MAX, Azumaya atrapa a Takato en su vergonzoso estado de ebriedad y lo usa para chantajearlo. 

A cambio del silencio de Azumaya, Azumaya dice: "¡Por favor, déjame abrazarte....! Abrázame, ¿quién fue el número 1 más abrazable?". ¡¿Qué demonios está diciendo?! Esta serie también incluye una gran cantidad de otras historias eróticas de alto suspenso</es_ES>
        <zh_Hans>西条高人自8岁时进入演艺圈起，就一直生活在众人的赞誉和聚光灯之下。浸淫在娱乐圈里许久，高人的性格变得傲慢而冷漠，但从另一方面来说，常年和普通社会脱节令他也有着意外单纯和天真的一面。高人有一个他引以为傲的荣誉——连续5年蝉联“最想被拥抱的男人”排行榜第一位，然而今年，高人胜利的宝座却被一个名叫东谷准太的新人抢走了。
东谷准太虽然入行没多久，却有着意外高涨的人气，性格温和的他深受粉丝和同僚们的欢迎。不服气的高人处处找准太的麻烦，却在一次意外中在准太面前暴露了自己不为人知的一面而留下了把柄在准太的手中。</zh_Hans>
        <zh_Hant>娛樂圈裡許久，高人的性格變得傲慢而冷漠，但從另一方面來說，常年和普通社會脫節令他也有著意外單純和天真的一面。高人有一個他引以為傲的榮譽——連續5年蟬聯「最想被擁抱的男人」排行榜第一位，然而今年，高人勝利的寶座卻被一個名叫東谷准太的新人搶走了。
東谷准太雖然入行沒多久，卻有著意外高漲的人氣，性格溫和的他深受粉絲和同僚們的歡迎。不服氣的高人處處找准太的麻煩，卻在一次意外中在准太面前暴露了自己不為人知的一面而留下了把柄在准太的手中。</zh_Hant>
        <vi_VN>Takato Saijyo là người đã cai trị ngành công nghiệp thần tượng “Most Huggable” trong 5 năm, cho đến khi có một tân binh mới Junta Azumaya vào nghề. Takato luôn bị mọi người coi là một kẻ khó tính nhưng trong khi đó Junta lại được nhiều người hâm mộ ca tụng có nụ cười vô cùng quyến rũ. Từ đó vị trí của Takato đã bị Junta giành mất. Toàn bộ thất bại đó đã làm Takato chìm đắm trong cơn say của men rượu và chính vì hành động này đã thu hút được Junta. Junta đã moi móc những thông tin từ quá khứ của Takato để "tống tình" Takato.</vi_VN>
    </synopsis>
    <information>
        <synonyms>
            <en_Latn>Dakaichi</en_Latn>
            <en_Latn>Dakaretai Otoko No.1 ni Odosareteimasu.</en_Latn>
            <en_Latn>Dakaretai Otoko Ichii ni Odosarete Imasu.</en_Latn>
            <ar_001 />
            <id_ID />
            <en_US>My Number One!</en_US>
            <en_US>The Most Huggable Man Has Threatened Me</en_US>
            <ja_JP>抱いち</ja_JP>
            <ja_JP>だかいち</ja_JP>
            <de_DE />
            <ko_KR />
            <fr_FR />
            <pt_PT />
            <ru_RU>DAKAICHI. Мой номер 1</ru_RU>
            <ru_RU>Загроза Для Хлопця No.1</ru_RU>
            <ru_RU>Загроза Для Хлопця №1</ru_RU>
            <es_ES />
            <zh_Hans />
            <zh_Hant />
            <vi_VN />
        </synonyms>
        <type>
            <en_US>TV</en_US>
            <id_ID>Serial TV</id_ID>
        </type>
        <status>
            <en_US>Aired</en_US>
            <id_ID>Ditayangkan</id_ID>
        </status>
        <serialGenre>
            <en_US>Drama</en_US>
            <en_US>Slice of Life</en_US>
            <en_US>Romance</en_US>
            <en_US>Mature</en_US>
            <en_US>Comedy</en_US>
            <id_ID>Drama</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Potongan Kehidupan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Romansa</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Dewasa</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Komedi</id_ID>
        </serialGenre>
        <serialTags>
            <en_US>Acting</en_US>
            <en_US>Adult Couples</en_US>
            <en_US>Blackmail</en_US>
            <en_US>Showbiz</en_US>
            <en_US>Shounen-Ai</en_US>
            <en_US>Yaoi</en_US>
            <en_US>Hentai</en_US>
            <en_US>Slapstick</en_US>
            <en_US>Eroticism</en_US>
            <en_US>Diva</en_US>
            <en_US>Idol</en_US>
            <en_US>Theater</en_US>
            <en_US>Tsundere</en_US>
            <en_US>Anal</en_US>
            <en_US>Masturbation</en_US>
            <en_US>Outdoors</en_US>
            <en_US>Softcore</en_US>
            <en_US>LGBTQ Issues</en_US>
            <en_US>Work</en_US>
            <en_US>Yandere</en_US>
            <id_ID>Akting</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Pasangan dewasa</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Pemerasan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Showbiz</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Shounen-Ai</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Yaoi</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Hentai</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Dagelan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Erotik</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Diva</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Idola</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Teater</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Tsundere</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Anal</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Onani</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Luar Ruangan</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Softcore</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Masalah LGBTQ</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Kerja</id_ID>
            <id_ID>Yandere</id_ID>
        </serialTags>
        <releaseSeason>
            <en_US>Fall</en_US>
            <id_ID>Gugur</id_ID>
            <ja_JP>秋</ja_JP>
            <ko_KR>여름</ko_KR>
            <zh_Hans>秋天</zh_Hans>
            <zh_Hant>秋天</zh_Hant>
        </releaseSeason>
        <releaseYear>2018</releaseYear>
        <episode>13</episode>
        <releaseDate>2018-10-06</releaseDate>
        <endDate>2018-12-29</endDate>
        <duration>25</duration>
        <totalDuration>325</totalDuration>
        <studio>CloverWorks</studio>
        <rating>R18+</rating>
        <isNsfw>true</isNsfw>
        <adaptation>
            <en_US>Manga</en_US>
            <id_ID>Manga</id_ID>
        </adaptation>
        <country>
            <en_US>Japan</en_US>
            <id_ID>Jepang</id_ID>
        </country>
    </information>
    <scores>
        <aniDB>
            <id>13979</id>
            <score>4.45</score>
        </aniDB>
        <AniList>
            <id>101381</id>
            <score>68</score>
        </AniList>
        <AnimePlanet>
            <url>https://www.anime-planet.com/anime/dakaichi-im-being-harassed-by-the-sexiest-man-of-the-year</url>
            <id>9887</id>
            <score>4.089</score>
        </AnimePlanet>
        <ANN>
            <id>20808</id>
            <score>6.392</score>
        </ANN>
        <aniSearch>
            <url>https://www.anisearch.com/anime/13516,dakaretai-otoko-ichii-ni-odosarete-imasu</url>
            <id>13516</id>
            <score>73</score>
        </aniSearch>
        <Annict>
            <id>6147</id>
            <score>84.22</score>
        </Annict>
        <IMDb>
            <code>tt9085692</code>
            <score>6.7</score>
        </IMDb>
        <KinoPoisk>
            <id>1201279</id>
            <score>6.982</score>
        </KinoPoisk>
        <Kitsu>
            <slug>dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu.</slug>
            <id>41151</id>
            <score>78.87</score>
        </Kitsu>
        <LiveChart>
            <id>7.81</id>
            <score>7.81</score>
        </LiveChart>
        <MyAnimeList>
            <id>37597</id>
            <score>7.41</score>
        </MyAnimeList>
        <MyShows>
            <id>58538</id>
            <score>4.04</score>
        </MyShows>
        <Nautiljon>
            <url>https://www.nautiljon.com/animes/dakaretai+otoko+1-i+ni+odosarete+imasu..html</url>
            <score>8.26</score>
        </Nautiljon>
        <Notify>
            <base64>XyjgVximR</base64>
            <score>7.05</score>
        </Notify>
        <OtakOtaku>
            <id />
            <score />
        </OtakOtaku>
        <Shikimori>
            <id>37597</id>
            <moved>true</moved>
            <newId>z37597</newId>
            <score>7.41</score>
        </Shikimori>
        <SIMKL>
            <id>792735</id>
            <score>8.4</score>
        </SIMKL>
        <TMDB>
            <url>https://www.themoviedb.org/tv/82867-dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu</url>
            <id>82867</id>
            <score>93</score>
        </TMDB>
        <Trakt>
            <url>https://trakt.tv/shows/dakaichi-i-m-being-harassed-by-the-sexiest-man-of-the-year</url>
            <id>136219</id>
            <score>74</score>
        </Trakt>
        <TVTime>
            <id>353837</id>
            <score>8.54</score>
        </TVTime>
    </scores>
    <updatedDate>2020-08-04T12:28:39+07:00</updatedDate>
    <fansub>
        <idn>
            <Aibou />
            <Aizukara />
            <Allsub />
            <Alter />
            <AnimeGokil />
            <AniToki />
            <AoiTenshi />
            <Arks />
            <ASubs />
            <AWSubs />
            <Bentoo />
            <Caramel />
            <Cijanepoi />
            <Conan />
            <DAnimeSubs />
            <Del />
            <DNFI />
            <Durandal />
            <EmotPekmen />
            <Excalibur />
            <exTonan />
            <Gantz />
            <Gin />
            <Haruna />
            <Haruzora />
            <HunterNoSekai>https://www.huntersekai.website/search/label/Dakaretai%20Otoko%201-i%20ni%20Odosarete%20Imasu</HunterNoSekai>
            <IA />
            <Inazumaotoshi />
            <Indis />
            <Inform0930 />
            <Isekai />
            <Junk />
            <Kazefuri />
            <Kinshiru />
            <KO />
            <Kopaja />
            <LCC />
            <MangaNekoTranslation />
            <Melody />
            <Mite />
            <Nanairo />
            <Neo />
            <OPLovers />
            <Ougi />
            <Panagayan />
            <Pendekar />
            <Pucuk />
            <Quinime />
            <RevieXion />
            <Samehadaku />
            <SilverYasha />
            <Sora />
            <TTOD />
            <Vedifi />
            <Warung />
            <Wibu />
            <Yuki />
            <Zen />
        </idn>
        <eng>
            <Horrible>https://horriblesubs.info/shows/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu</Horrible>
        </eng>
    </fansub>
    <fanshare>
        <idn>
            <AniBatch />
            <AnimeKompi />
            <AnimeSAVE />
            <Bakacan>https://bakacan.id/anime/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu/</Bakacan>
            <Drivenime>https://drivenime.com/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu-subtitle-indonesia-batch/</Drivenime>
            <Hinime>https://hinime.com/dakaretai-otoko-1-ni-odosarete-imasu/</Hinime>
            <Koenime>https://www.koenime.com/dakaoto-sub-indo/</Koenime>
            <Kusonime>https://kusonime.com/dakaichi-batch-subtitle-indonesia/</Kusonime>
            <Mikanime>https://mikanime.com/dakaretai-otoko-sub-indo/</Mikanime>
            <Moenime />
            <Ryuukoi />
            <WibuDesu />
        </idn>
        <eng>
            <AnimeKayo>https://animekayo.com/?s=Dakaretai+Otoko+1-i+ni+Odosarete+Imasu</AnimeKayo>
        </eng>
    </fanshare>
    <fanstream>
        <idn>
            <AnimeIndoNET>http://animeindo.moe/anime/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu</AnimeIndoNET>
            <anoBoy>https://anoboy.us/anime/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu/</anoBoy>
            <Gomunime>https://gomunime.com/anime/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu/</Gomunime>
            <Moeclip />
            <Neonime />
            <Onnime>https://onnime.net/anime/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu.DG8mMv0Q/</Onnime>
            <OtakuIndo />
        </idn>
        <eng>
            <fourAnime>https://4anime.to/anime/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu</fourAnime>
            <nineAnime>https://9anime.ru/watch/dakaichi-im-being-harassed-by-the-sexiest-man-of-the-year.567m</nineAnime>
            <AnimeDaisuki>https://animedaisuki.moe/anime/382/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu</AnimeDaisuki>
            <AnimeTwist>https://twist.moe/a/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu/1</AnimeTwist>
            <Animeflix />
            <AnimeHeaven>https://animeheaven.ru/detail/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu-sub.54859</AnimeHeaven>
            <Animelon />
            <Animeultima>https://www1.animeultima.to/a/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu_346601</Animeultima>
            <AniWatch>https://aniwatch.me/anime/931</AniWatch>
            <GogoAnime>https://gogoanimes.co/category/dakaretai-otoko-1-i-ni-odosarete-imasu</GogoAnime>
            <WonderfulSubs>https://www.wonderfulsubs.com/watch/dakaichiimbeingharassedbythesexiestmanoftheyear</WonderfulSubs>
        </eng>
    </fanstream>
    <library>
        <Nyaa>https://nyaa.si/view/914467</Nyaa>
        <PerpusIndo />
    </library>
    <signature>
        <name>Yamashita Kazuhito</name>
        <username>@YamashitaKazuhito</username>
        <discordId>584207131671134200</discordId>
        <submissionDateTime>2020-06-23T12:18:34+07:00</submissionDateTime>
        <sign>RGlnaXRhbGx5IFNpZ25lZCBieSBZYW1hc2hpdGEgS2F6dWhpdG8gQCBNYXVyaXRpdXMKQXNzaXN0ZWQgYnkgTmF0c3UgVGFkYW1hIChAbmF0dGFkYXN1KQ==</sign>
    </signature>
</ryuuganime>